Rochester Transit Company Arbitration Files 5104
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Rochester Transit Company Arbitration Files
1950
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Rochester Transit Company
5104
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Arbitration hearing before Albert I. Cornsweet, Chairman, Phillip B. Willauer and Hyman G. Gould in Rochester, New York from June 20, 1950 to June 29, 1950. The issues were: 1. Ability to pay. 2. Hourly wage rates. 3. Arbitration. 4. Hours. 5. Extra men. 6. Overtime. 7. Retroactivity.
3117822
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 25, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 28, 2016
Scope and Contents
Arbitration hearing before Albert I. Cornsweet, Chairman, Phillip B. Willauer and Hyman G. Gould in Rochester, New York from June 20, 1950 to June 29, 1950. The issues were:
1. Ability to pay.
2. Hourly wage rates.
3. Arbitration.
4. Hours.
5. Extra men.
6. Overtime.
7. Retroactivity.
The collection is arranged in four series: Transcripts, Union Exhibits, Company Exhibits, and Award.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arbitration, Industrial--United States--Sources.; Cornsweet, Albert I.; Rochester Transit Company
3117822
- Arbitration-RTC v. Union, Curtin for RTC, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Arbitration between Rochester Transit Corporation and Amalgamated Association of Street and Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America. Volume 2, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Arbitration Between Rochester Transit Corporation and Division 282 of the Amalgamated Association of Street and Electric railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Vol. 3, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Proceedings, Arbitration Between Rochester Transit Corporation and Amalgamated Association of Street Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Arbitration Between Rochester Transit Corporation and Amalgamated Association of Street Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Scope and Contents
  June 27th
- Arbitration Between Rochester Transit Corporation and Amalgamated Association of Street Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  June 29
- Company Exhibits, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Proposed and Final Agreements, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Union Exhibits, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Arbitration Submission, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Award and Opinion of Arbitration Board, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Arbitrators' Correspondence, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 12)